<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RedLetterProducts>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>5850</Id>
    <Title>An Amphibious Vehicle Tour of London for Two</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>View London the amphibious way.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>An Amphibious Tour of London for Two</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>LFTFT</ExpRef>
    <Type>Main</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>55</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>45.83</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>131</Id>
        <Name>London Duck Tours - London</Name>
        <County>London</County>
        <Town>London</Town>
        <PostCode>SE1 7NJ</PostCode>
        <Latitude>51.50285</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-0.11694</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>London and South East</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>South Bank, London</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Culture</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>London Sightseeing &amp; Tours</SectionName>
    <Priority>1</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Take a tour of London with a difference</Fact>
      <Fact>Tour the city in a famous DUKWS war vehicle</Fact>
      <Fact>From patrolling the streets of London, your vehicle will plunge into the Thames</Fact>
      <Fact>See the sights of the capital from an entirely new perspective</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Get out the binoculars and prepare for a unique perspective of the capital with amphibious London tours. Experiences in London don't come much better than this! These fascinating vehicles were originally used in wartime, transporting troops and cargo across the waters straight onto land. Famous sights along the way will include Big Ben, Houses of Parliament, Buckingham Palace and The Ritz. The guide will provide an entertaining commentary, giving a unique view of London's history, as well as some riveting facts about the DUKW (known as The Duck). After passing The Tate Gallery, the whole vehicle will dive into the Thames and take a swim, before climbing back up onto the streets of London towards Lambeth Palace and London Eye.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Dates run throughout the year with various time slots throughout the day (from 10am to 6pm). Please give at least 72 hours booking notice.</Availability>
    <Weather>The weather should not affect this experience, but any cancellations are made with your safety in mind.</Weather>
    <Duration>The tour lasts approximately 75 minutes, 45 of which are spent on the road and 30 on the river. Please arrive a few minutes prior to departure as allowances cannot be made for missed departures and tickets are non transferable and non refundable.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>75 mins</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>A maximum of 30 passengers share the vehicle.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily />
    <DressCode />
    <AnyOtherInfo>Please take your booking confirmation letter with you on the day of your experience in order to participate.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>This experience is for two people, minimum age 4. Children between the ages of 4 and 12 are accepted but must be accompanied by a voucher holding adult (aged 18 or over). Prams and pushchairs are not permitted on board.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Your experience is held with London Duck Tours from Chicheley Street, London SE1 7PJ.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Exit Waterloo (Northern line) on London Underground via the exit heading for BA London Eye. If in Beleverdere Road, turn left into Chicheley Street and if in York Road, turn right into Chicheley Street (behind the BA London Eye, opposite All Bar One) to start your tour.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>An-Amphibious-Tour-Of-London-For-Two</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/LFTFT/An-Amphibious-Tour-Of-London-For-Two</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/LFTFO_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/LFTFO_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>LFTFO_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords>amphibious,tour,london,river,swim,sightseeing,duck,frog</Keywords>
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>5854</Id>
    <Title>Thames Dinner Cruise for Two</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Great music, great food and great views.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>A Dinner Cruise on The Thames for Two</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>BATDC</ExpRef>
    <Type>Main</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>175</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>145.83</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>18</Id>
        <Name>Bateaux London - Embankment</Name>
        <County>London</County>
        <Town>Embankment</Town>
        <PostCode>WC2N 6NU</PostCode>
        <Latitude>51.50733</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-0.12139</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>London and South East</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Embankment, London</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Culture</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Thames Cruises</SectionName>
    <Priority>1</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>A welcome cocktail as you board</Fact>
      <Fact>Sensational views of London as you cruise down the Thames</Fact>
      <Fact>Four-course à la carte meal of British based cuisine</Fact>
      <Fact>Cabaret entertainment and after dinner dancing</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Should you go sightseeing on the Thames? Or cut to the chase and have a tasty dinner somewhere? With this experience you can do both on this stunning day out. Board Bateaux London's river cruiser from the glass pontoon at Embankment Pier. Then relax on board and enjoy a welcome drink followed by a four-course a la carte meal and tea or coffee, whilst cruising past the Houses of Parliament, the Tower of London and many more iconic landmarks. A blend of jazz is performed during the cruise by the resident band. Then end the day out by enjoying some after dinner dancing with music from the 60s, 70s, 80s, 90s and hits of today.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Cruises are available daily from April to December and Tuesday to Saturday from January to March. Bank holidays are excluded.</Availability>
    <Weather>Bateaux London cruises operate in all weather conditions.</Weather>
    <Duration>Board from 6.45pm or 7.30pm to depart at 7.15pm or 8pm. Return to Embankment Pier at 10pm or 10.45pm. Exact boarding time will be e-mailed 24 hours in advance of the booking. Late boarding is not possible, the boat has to leave on time.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>3 hrs</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>The Symphony seats a maximum of 220 diners.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Spectators are welcome to wave you off from the river bank.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Please dress smartly. Gentlemen are encouraged to wear a jacket and tie. No shorts, jeans/denim or trainers/sports shoes are permitted and the venue reserve the right to refuse entry to anyone inappropriately dressed with no refund offered.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Any additional drinks, including the selection of wines available are payable directly on the day. Smoking is permitted on the outside deck only. Feel free to bring a camera to record the sights. Evouchers are issued once a booking has been made.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Minimum age is 15. Under 18's must be accompanied by an adult. Vegetarian meal options are available. Unfortunately the boat doesn't have full wheelchair access.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Bateaux London cruises depart from Embankment Pier, Embankment, London WC2N 6NU. Telephone 0207 6951800.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Embankment Pier is located on the corner of Hungerford Bridge at Victoria Embankment, close to Embankment underground station. Cross the road from the station and head down the Bateaux gantry on your left into the reception area. The closest chargeable car parking is normally available at Spring Gardens SW1A 2BN.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>A-Dinner-Cruise-On-The-Thames-For-Two</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/BATDC/A-Dinner-Cruise-On-The-Thames-For-Two</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/BATDL_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/BATDL_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>BATDL_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords>dinner,cruise,thames,couple,couples,two,meal,food,dine,sightsee,barge,boat,dance,embankment,pier,london,parliament,tower,bridge,tate,tower,london,cocktail,drink,cabaret,entertainment,band,music,tourist,evening,night,romance,cuisine</Keywords>
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>5904</Id>
    <Title>Aromatherapy Massage in Cambridgeshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Relaxation has never felt this good...</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>An Aromatherapy Massage</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>AESAA</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>50</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>41.67</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>37</Id>
        <Name>Elaine's Of Brampton Aromatherapy - Brampton</Name>
        <County>Cambridgeshire</County>
        <Town>Brampton</Town>
        <PostCode>PE28 4RA</PostCode>
        <Latitude>52.32432</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-0.22917</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>East</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Huntingdon, Cambridgeshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Pampering</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Wellbeing, Relaxation &amp; Fitness</SectionName>
    <Priority>0</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Recieve a consultation with a trained therapist</Fact>
      <Fact>Indulge in a refreshing aromatherapy massage</Fact>
      <Fact>Enjoy the tranquil scent of essential oils</Fact>
      <Fact>Leave feeling brand new</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>After discussing any specific needs or requirements with a professional therapist, enjoy the tranquillity of a relaxing aromatherapy massage. The refreshing scent comes from the essential oils, extracted from seeds, plants and flowers to gently massage away any cares and worries. This treatment is a great stress buster and the perfect remedy for anyone with a busy, demanding life.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Monday to Friday from 10am to 6pm.</Availability>
    <Weather />
    <Duration>Your massage will last for one hour but please allow one and a half hours at the venue. You'll be so relaxed afterwards that you may want to rest for a short while before driving.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>1 hr</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>Naturally this is a one to one session, just you and your aromatherapist.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily />
    <DressCode>You will be wrapped in towels during your massage. You can keep your underwear on if you prefer not to be naked.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Please shower at home before your massage. There is a health consultation prior to the massage, you may be asked to divulge personal information. If you are receiving treatment for an illness it is recommended that you consult your GP prior to treatment.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Please inform us in advance if you are (or have been) recently pregnant, have any medical conditions/allergies, or have had surgery recently. Information given will dictate which oils are used.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Your experience is held with Elaine's of Brampton at The Courtyard, 115 High Street, Brampton, Cambridgeshire PE28 4RA.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Please contact the therapist directly if you require further directions.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>An-Aromatherapy-Massage</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/AESAA/An-Aromatherapy-Massage</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/BYEME_3.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/BYEME_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>BYEME_3.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>5909</Id>
    <Title>Gliding Flight in Northamptonshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Soar in silence on a breathtaking flight.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>An Aerotow Gliding Flight</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>AGAAA</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>100</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>83.33</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>13</Id>
        <Name>Banbury Gliding Club Limited</Name>
        <County>Northamptonshire</County>
        <Town>Brackley</Town>
        <PostCode>NN13 5NS</PostCode>
        <Latitude>52.02968</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-1.21062</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Midlands</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Brackley, Northamptonshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Flying</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Microlights &amp; Gliding</SectionName>
    <Priority>1</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Take to the skies in in a glider</Fact>
      <Fact>Fly freely in the thermal currents</Fact>
      <Fact>Enjoy beautiful views of the countryside</Fact>
      <Fact>Take over the flight controls (at the pilot's discretion)</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Glimpse into the peaceful and somewhat diverse world of gliding with this aerotow flight in Northamptonshire. Following a discussion on the aircraft and flight safety, board a dual-controlled glider with an instructor ready for take-off. The glider is initially towed by a light aircraft to heights of around 2,000 ft, before the rope is detached and the craft majestically soars in a birdlike fashion in the thermal currents. Revel in the amazing views of the rolling countryside below and during the flight (at the discretion of the pilot), take charge of the controls to truly enjoy the unrivalled joys of flying.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Most weekends and bank holidays throughout the year, and on a few weekdays during mid-summer. The venue is closed over the Christmas period. Summer weekends are particularly busy, book at least six weeks in advance.</Availability>
    <Weather>Gliding is weather dependent and conditions can affect flight duration and time. It is essential to call the venue for a weather check: for morning bookings call the day before, for afternoon or evening bookings call on the day before setting out.</Weather>
    <Duration>Flight length depends on prevailing thermal conditions. As a guide, the flight should last for between 12 and 20 minutes, but expect to spend a few hours on-site. Please arrive a few minutes in advance and make your way straight to the clubhouse.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>20 mins</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>The briefing may be shared, your flight is held on a one-to-one basis with the instructor.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Spectators are welcome. A camera or a pair of binoculars will come in handy.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Wear flat-soled shoes and bring a jumper with you in case it gets cold at higher altitudes. Bring gloves in winter. Sunglasses are recommended all year round.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Please remember: in an active airfield, aircraft always retain right of way. You must stay in notified areas unless accompanied by a member of staff, and steer clear of craft and equipment at all times.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Min age 11. Max weight 16st. Height 4' 11'' to 6'4''. You can't fly if you suffer from epilepsy, fainting or any condition that could endanger the flight. Disabilities need not be a bar if you can follow instructions and climb in/out of glider unaided.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Banbury Gliding Club, Hinton Airfield, near Hinton In The Hedges, Brackley, Northamptonshire NN13 5NS. Telephone 0333 044 0134 or 07981 103159 (Sat/Sun only).</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>From the A422 between Brackley and Banbury: follow the signs to Hinton Airfield (NOT Hinton-in-the-Hedges). Once you have entered the airfield follow the track to the left and then first right. You can park outside the skydiving club, the clubhouse is on your right. On arrival please ring the launch point mobile 07981 103159 and somebody will escort you to the launch point.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>An-Aerotow-Gliding-Flight</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/AGAAA/An-Aerotow-Gliding-Flight</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/XGLIA_5.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/XGLIA_5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>XGLIA_5.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>5989</Id>
    <Title>Aromatherapy Massage in Warwickshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Relaxation has never felt this good.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>An Aromatherapy Massage</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>ASHAA</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>50</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>41.67</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>89</Id>
        <Name>Efstop Ltd (@ Salus Natural Therapy Cent - Stratford Upon Avon</Name>
        <County>Warwickshire</County>
        <Town>Stratford Upon Avon</Town>
        <PostCode>CV37 6QW</PostCode>
        <Latitude>52.19452</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-1.70935</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Midlands</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Stratford-upon-Avon, Warwickshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Pampering</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Wellbeing, Relaxation &amp; Fitness</SectionName>
    <Priority>0</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Talk through personal preferences with a therapist</Fact>
      <Fact>Enjoy the reviving scent of essential oils</Fact>
      <Fact>Recharge with a soothing aromatherapy massage</Fact>
      <Fact>And take home a bottle of relaxing lavender oil</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Aromatherapy massage is a great stress-reliever and a perfect way to unwind. After a consultation, enjoy a refreshing massage session. Feel all cares being massaged away and enjoy the luxurious scent of the essential oils, extracted from plants, flowers and seeds. We guarantee that 'me time' has never felt (or smelt!) so good. Take home a bottle of lavender oil to continue the rejuvenation at home.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Daily (except Tuesdays and national holidays) throughout the year.</Availability>
    <Weather />
    <Duration>The experience lasts for between one and one and a half hours, including your consultation. You'll be so relaxed afterwards that you may want to rest for a short while before driving.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>1 hr</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>Naturally this is a one to one session, just you and your aromatherapist.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily />
    <DressCode>You will be wrapped in towels during your massage. You can keep your underwear on if you prefer not to be naked.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Please shower at home before your massage. There is a health consultation prior to the massage, you may be asked to divulge personal information. If you are receiving treatment for an illness it is recommended that you consult your GP prior to treatment.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Please inform the aromatherapist in advance if you are (or have recently been) pregnant, or if you have any medical conditions/allergies, as this will dictate which oils are used.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Your experience is held with a therapist at Salus Natural Therapy Centre, 30/31 Henley Street, Stratford Upon Avon, Warwickshire. Telephone 01789 204775 or 0845 217 9093.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>The centre is located at the rear of Flyntz Hairdressers (on Windsor Street), through a wrought iron gateway at the side of the photography shop called WINK.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>An-Aromatherapy-Massage</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/ASHAA/An-Aromatherapy-Massage</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/ASHAA_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/ASHAA_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>ASHAA_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>6145</Id>
    <Title>Extended Rally Driving Experience at Westbury, Northamptonshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>A wild time of skids, power slides and artful handbrake turns.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>Extended Rally Driving</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>BGAFW</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>299</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>249.17</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>24</Id>
        <Name>Bill Gwynne Rallyschool International - Brackley</Name>
        <County>Northamptonshire</County>
        <Town>Brackley</Town>
        <PostCode>NN13 5YD</PostCode>
        <Latitude>52.03745</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-1.10095</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Midlands</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Brackley, Northamptonshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Driving</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Rally Driving &amp; Drifting</SectionName>
    <Priority>0</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Learn about skidding, power slides and the art of handbrake turns</Fact>
      <Fact>Take on the challenging rally stage in Northamptonshire</Fact>
      <Fact>Take part in six driving sessions</Fact>
      <Fact>Work up an appetite, lunch is included</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Few things get the adrenaline pumping like racing a rally car round an authentic rally track. And this all day rally driving experience at Westbury, Northamptonshire does just that. After a safety briefing, get behind the wheel of two different cars over six driving sessions to fully experience the controlled chaos of racing a rally car. A professional driving instructor is on hand with tips and advice, and will help you learn handbrake turns, power slides and even skid control. Race the front-wheel drive Nissan Micra, and the rear-wheel drive Ford Escort Mk2, to experience how both of these systems handle the rally stage's loose-surface terrain. This rally driving experience is essential for any driving enthusiast.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Saturdays and occasional weekdays once or twice a month throughout the year. Dates fill very quickly; book at least four weeks in advance.</Availability>
    <Weather>Driving may be cancelled or curtailed in extreme weather conditions which would make driving at speed dangerous. Please call the venue the day before to check final arrangements.</Weather>
    <Duration>Lasts around seven hours. This includes a briefing, tuition, driving time, lunch and debrief. Please arrive a few minutes prior to the booked start time.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>7 hrs</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>Total numbers will vary but there will be a maximum of six people in your group. During the driving bit, only you and the instructor will be in the vehicle.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Up to two spectators are welcome for £10 each, which includes lunch and refreshments. Please book and pay for spectators a minimum of seven days in advance, direct with the venue.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Wear flat shoes which are comfortable for driving. Helmets are provided. Any other special clothing you need is also provided.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>High-speed passenger rides can be purchased on the day, subject to availability.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Min height 5'2'' and max height is 6'6''. Maximum weight is 18 stone. A driving licence isn't required to take part, but you do need to be a confident driver with plenty of experience driving manual cars.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Bill Gwynne Rallyschool International, Turweston Aerodrome, Westbury, near Brackley, Northampton NN13 5YD. Telephone 01280 705570. Only in the event you dont receive an answer, call 07769 551583.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Exit the M1, junction 15a, follow A43 for Oxford, passing Towcester, Silverstone and Syresham. From the dual carriageway, turn left for the aerodrome where signposted. After a mile or so, turn right into Turweston Aerodrome and wait at the meeting point on the left hand side of runway. Please exercise caution at all times when on site - beware of potholes and when crossing the runway.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>Extended-Rally-Driving-At-Westbury-Northamptonshire</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/BGAFW/Extended-Rally-Driving-At-Westbury-Northamptonshire</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/BGAFW_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/BGAFW_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>BGAFW_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>6146</Id>
    <Title>Rally Driving in Northamptonshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Skids, power slides and handbrake turns around challenging stages.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>Introductory Rally Driving</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>BGAHH</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>189</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>157.50</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>24</Id>
        <Name>Bill Gwynne Rallyschool International - Brackley</Name>
        <County>Northamptonshire</County>
        <Town>Brackley</Town>
        <PostCode>NN13 5YD</PostCode>
        <Latitude>52.03745</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-1.10095</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Midlands</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Brackley, Northamptonshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Driving</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Rally Driving &amp; Drifting</SectionName>
    <Priority>0</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Master the art of power slides, handbrake turns and skid cause and control</Fact>
      <Fact>Drive a MkII Escort or a Nissan Micra around the challenging rally stage</Fact>
      <Fact>Pick up priceless tips from a professional instructor</Fact>
      <Fact>Includes lunch</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Many thousands of driving enthusiasts opt for expert tuition at the Bill Gwynne Rally School. The centre, established in 1983, provides a great location for aspiring rally drivers and rally driving enthusiasts. FindByKeyword out the physical and mental demands of negotiating a challenging rally stage and discover the secrets of power slides, handbrake turns and skid cause and control. Following a familiarisation ride from the expert tutor, hop into either a rear wheel drive MkII Escort or a front wheel drive Nissan Micra, and perfect the power slide during two six-lap driving sessions.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Saturdays twice a month plus occasional Wednesdays and Thursdays. Saturdays are always busy - book at least six weeks in advance.</Availability>
    <Weather>Driving may be cancelled or curtailed in extreme weather conditions which would make driving at speed dangerous. Please call the venue the day before to check final arrangements.</Weather>
    <Duration>Lasts around four hours including a briefing, tuition, driving time and a debrief. Please arrive a few minutes prior to the booked start time.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>4 hrs</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>There will be up to six participants in your group. Total numbers at the venue will vary. During the driving bit, only you and the instructor will be in the vehicle.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Up to two spectators are welcome for £5 each. This must be booked and paid a minimum of seven days in advance, direct with the venue.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Wear flat shoes which are comfortable for driving. Helmets will be provided on the day, but if you have your own you're welcome to bring it along.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>High-speed passenger rides can be purchased on the day, subject to availability.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Min height 5'2'' and max height is 6'6''. Maximum weight is 18 stone. You don't need a driving licence to take part, but do need to be a confident driver with plenty of experience driving manual cars.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Bill Gwynne Rallyschool International, Turweston Aerodrome, Westbury, near Brackley, Northampton NN13 5YD. Telephone 01280 705570. Only in the event you dont receive an answer, call 07769 551583.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Exit the M1, junction 15a, follow A43 for Oxford, passing Towcester, Silverstone and Syresham. From the dual carriageway, turn left for the aerodrome where signposted. After a mile or so, turn right into Turweston Aerodrome and wait at the meeting point on the left hand side of runway. Please exercise caution at all times when on site - beware of potholes and when crossing the runway.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>Rally-Driving-Experience-At-Bill-Gwynne-Rally-School</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/BGAHH/Rally-Driving-Experience-At-Bill-Gwynne-Rally-School</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/BGAFW_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/BGAFW_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>BGAFW_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>6218</Id>
    <Title>Gliding Flight in Buckinghamshire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>Soar in silence on a breathtaking flight.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>An Aerotow Gliding Flight</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>BOOAA</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>100</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>83.33</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>25</Id>
        <Name>Booker Gliding Club Ltd - Marlow</Name>
        <County>Buckinghamshire</County>
        <Town>Marlow</Town>
        <PostCode>SL7 3DP</PostCode>
        <Latitude>51.61002</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-0.79960</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Home Counties</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Marlow, Buckinghamshire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Flying</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Microlights &amp; Gliding</SectionName>
    <Priority>1</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Enjoy the peace and tranquillity of gliding</Fact>
      <Fact>Ride the thermal currents</Fact>
      <Fact>Expert instruction from a qualified instructor</Fact>
      <Fact>Take over the piloting duties (at the instructors discretion)</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Enjoy the peace and tranquillity of an aerotow gliding flight in Marlow, Buckinghamshire. Kick off with a full flight safety briefing before jumping aboard a dual-controlled glider with an expert pilot. Once ready, the glider is towed into the air by a light aircraft, and when at an altitude of approximately 2,000 ft, the rope is dropped and the aircraft is free to elegantly roam the skies using thermal currents. Enjoy sensational birds-eye views of the Chilterns below and during the flight (at the pilot's discretion), there may be a chance to take over the controls and become an honorary pilot.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Seven days a week throughout the year, including bank holidays. The club is closed during the Christmas period. Weekends are particularly busy - book at least six weeks in advance. Bookings are more likely to be available on weekdays and weekday evenings.</Availability>
    <Weather>Gliding is weather dependent and it's crucial that you call the venue for a weather check. For morning bookings call the day before, for afternoon/evening bookings call before setting out (the office opens at 8.30am). Cancelled flights will be rebooked.</Weather>
    <Duration>The length of glider flights depends entirely on the prevailing thermals (currents of warmer air that provide the lift). As a guide, the aerotow flight should last for between 12 and 20 minutes.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>15 mins</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>The centre works on the ratio of one instructor to two pupils.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Spectators are welcome but must follow safety directions whilst on-site. A camera or a pair of binoculars will come in handy. Young children must be closely supervised at all times.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Wear flat-soled shoes and bring a jumper with you in case it gets cold at higher altitudes. Bring gloves in winter and sunglasses are recommended all year round.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Flying under the influence of alcohol is against the law. You'll be asked to sign a form to confirm you have not drunk alcohol and to state that you agree to comply with all operational rules and instructions.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Minimum age is 16. Minimum height is 5'', maximum is 6'4''. Minimum weight is 7 stone, maximum is 16 stone. You can't fly if you suffer from epilepsy, fainting or certain other physical or mental disabilities - check when booking.</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Booker Gliding Club at Wycombe Air Park, Marlow, Buckinghamshire, SL7 3DP. Telephone 01494 442501 or 529263.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere>Exit the M40 at junction 4 and travel along the A4010 Aylesbury Road, taking you off the roundabout past The Holiday Inn (John Hall Way). At the third mini roundabout turn left, signposted Lane End and Wycombe Air Park. Continue on Cressex Road (you will cross over the M40) and the air park lies one mile along on the right.</HowToGetThere>
    <PermaLink>An-Aerotow-Gliding-Flight</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/BOOAA/An-Aerotow-Gliding-Flight</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/XGLIA_3.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/XGLIA_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>XGLIA_3.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords>aerotow,gliding,fly,flight,sky,air,airborne,aerial,pilot,aircraft,speed</Keywords>
  </RedLetterProduct>
  <RedLetterProduct>
    <Id>6056</Id>
    <Title>30 Minute Helicopter Flight in Gloucestershire</Title>
    <InspirationalDescription>A completely different way of flying.</InspirationalDescription>
    <VoucherText>A 30 Minute Helicopter Trial Flight</VoucherText>
    <ExpRef>BAGIG</ExpRef>
    <Type>Sub</Type>
    <GeneralPrice>220</GeneralPrice>
    <PriceBeforeVAT>183.33</PriceBeforeVAT>
    <Venues>
      <Venue>
        <Id>27</Id>
        <Name>Patriot Aviation - Gloucester t/a Helifl - Cheltenham</Name>
        <County>Gloucestershire</County>
        <Town>Cheltenham</Town>
        <PostCode>GL51 6SR</PostCode>
        <Latitude>51.89450</Latitude>
        <Longitude>-2.16671</Longitude>
      </Venue>
    </Venues>
    <Territory>Midlands</Territory>
    <DisplayLocations>Cheltenham, Gloucestershire</DisplayLocations>
    <MainSectionName>Flying</MainSectionName>
    <SectionName>Helicopter Flights</SectionName>
    <Priority>0</Priority>
    <Facts>
      <Fact>Expert instruction from a qualified pilot</Fact>
      <Fact>Backwards, forwards, sideways, hovering</Fact>
      <Fact>Take the controls and pilot the helicopter</Fact>
      <Fact>Flying time can count towards a Private Pilot's Licence</Fact>
    </Facts>
    <WhatsIncluded>Come to Gloucestershire Airport for an exciting helicopter flight over the surrounding countryside. Meet the pilot on the ground who will give a brief on safety and flying techniques before boarding. Then climb into a dual-controlled training helicopter which will immediately impress with its vertical take-off. These craft are incredibly manoeuvrable and can turn on a pin forward, backward or sideways. At the pilot's discretion, confident learners can take over the controls, to really understand what it's like to command a flying machine.</WhatsIncluded>
    <Availability>Tuesday to Sunday throughout the year, excluding Christmas Day. Weekends are particularly busy, please book at least four weeks in advance.</Availability>
    <Weather>Helicopter flying is weather dependent, mainly due to wind speeds and cloud cover. It is CRUCIAL that you call for a weather check. For morning bookings call the venue the day before. For afternoon/evening bookings call on the day before setting out.</Weather>
    <Duration>The time spent in the helicopter is around 30 minutes from engines-on to engines-off. This includes warm-up, take-off and landing.</Duration>
    <ShortDuration>30 mins</ShortDuration>
    <HowManyPeople>Briefings may be shared. The flight is held one a one-to-one basis with the instructor.</HowManyPeople>
    <FriendsAndFamily>Spectators are welcome to watch you take off and land. A pair of binoculars or a camera will come in handy. The club lounge offers advantageous viewing over the airfield.</FriendsAndFamily>
    <DressCode>Please bear in mind that the cockpit can get quite warm and dress accordingly. Sunglasses are recommended all year round.</DressCode>
    <AnyOtherInfo>Flying time can count towards a Private Pilot's Licence. To qualify for a PPL you need a minimum of 45 hours dual-control flying, of which at least 10 hours must be solo flying.</AnyOtherInfo>
    <WhoCanTakePart>Minimum age is 12. Under 18's must be accompanied by a parent or guardian who will be required to sign a consent form. Minimum height is 5'. Maximum weight is 16 stone (102kg).</WhoCanTakePart>
    <WhereIsItHeld>Heliflight (UK) at Gloucestershire Airport (south side), Staverton, Cheltenham, Gloucester GL51 6SR.</WhereIsItHeld>
    <HowToGetThere />
    <PermaLink>A-Helicopter-Flight</PermaLink>
    <Url>https://www.redletterdays.co.uk/Experience/Ref/BAGIG/A-Helicopter-Flight</Url>
    <ImageUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img435/productlarge/CWATG_1.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <ThumbnailUrl>https://assets.redletterdays.co.uk/images/img140/productlarge/CWATG_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <LargeImageName>CWATG_1.jpg</LargeImageName>
    <IsSpecialOffer>False</IsSpecialOffer>
    <DeliveryTime>Options include Royal Mail First Class Post (3-5 working days) or next day courier delivery.</DeliveryTime>
    <DeliveryCost>You can select from three delivery options: Royal Mail First Class Post for £1.99, next day courier delivery for £5.95 or Saturday courier delivery for £24.95.</DeliveryCost>
    <Keywords />
  </RedLetterProduct>
</RedLetterProducts>